https://adulttoydiscounters.com/content/privacy-statement

> Privacy StatementPrivacy Statement The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.Safe Shopping at AdultToyDiscounters.comWe want you to feel completely secure when ordering from AdultToyDiscounters.com. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet.What Personal Information We CollectWe collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using the AdultToyDiscounters.com Web site. This information includes your email address and a password when you create your AdultToyDiscounters.com account. You can browse our online store without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of certain features. We may also ask for personal information when you contact our Customer Service. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.AdultToyDiscounters.com does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 18. If you are under 18 you are not allowed to shop, or view the pages here at AdultToyDiscounters.com.Purchase InformationWhen you make a purchase using a credit card, we collect your name, your billing address for the card, the card type, number, and expiration date. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s).When you create an account at of AdultToyDiscounters.com, you may change or delete this saved information anytime. Simply log in with your email address and password, then click "Billing Address & Credit Card," "Address Book" or "Email Address & Password" and edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.Cookies and Other Computer InformationWhen you visit AdultToyDiscounters.com, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our site so we can enhance and customize your online shopping experience.You can choose to shop at AdultToyDiscounters.com without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to take advantage of certain features of our site. These features include remembering your password (so you don't have to log in each time you visit), storing your shopping cart for later use and, in the future, providing a more personalized shopping experience. To shop without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)Other Times We May Collect Personal InformationFrom time to time, AdultToyDiscounters.com may conduct surveys and contests via our Web site, email, other media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.How We Use Your Personal InformationInformation we collect on AdultToyDiscounters.com may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:Deliver merchandise that you purchase onlineRegister you as a member of AdultToyDiscounters.comBill your credit card for your purchasesConfirm your ordersRespond to your customer-service inquiries or requestsCommunicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such noticesFind and stock the products you wantCustomize your shopping experienceHow You Can Control the Use of Your Personal InformationYou can modify or delete your personal information anytime. Simply go to Your Account. Log in with your email address and password, then click "Billing Address," and edit or delete whatever information you wish. Do not share your AdultToyDiscounters.com password with anyone. Other than on our site, AdultToyDiscounters.com will never ask you for your password.How We Protect the Security of Your Personal InformationThe security of your personal information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet.AdultToyDiscounters.com has also obtained a digital certificate from Verisign, Inc., a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secure portion of our site (which is any page containing any of your personal information), an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser window. If you click on this image, a small popup window displaying site-security information will appear. This certificate guarantees that your personal information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form to a AdultToyDiscounters.com Web server, not to some unknown or unauthorized server.Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you created an account at AdultToyDiscounters.com (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of AdultToyDiscounters.com will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to Your Account. Log in with your email address and password, then click "Email Address & Password" and enter a new password.We realize that making purchases at AdultToyDiscounters.com, or any other Web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our customer, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address, and credit-card information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally.We believe that you have a right to know, before shopping at AdultToyDiscounters.com or at any other time, exactly what information we might collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it.AdultToyDiscounters.com, ("we") do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. You have the right to control your personal information as you see fit. We collect only the personal information you allow us to collect, and then it is used only to help us serve you better.If you have an account at AdultToyDiscounters.com and you want to change, modify or delete any of your personal information, you can do so anytime by going to Your Account. Log in with your email address and password and edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.
